<u>Harlon Selser</u> (210) 288-6334

harlon.selser@outlook.com

Objective

Healthcare IT Professional with six years of former military service with an honorable discharge and expertise in system maintenance (hardware and software), troubleshooting, and repair. Experience in customer service with a focus on time management. Additional skills include inventory management, vendor relations, presentations, conducting training, and writing technical documentation.

Professional Experience

10/2019 -	Defense Health Agency (Contractor)
Present	Position held: Tier 1 Customer Service Representative
	 Troubleshooting user technical difficulties with applications and hardware, login resets, and end user support. Utilize and maintain ticket system and escalate tickets to appropriate departments and higher tiers. Common tickets include profile management, creating accounts, password resets, drive mapping, performance troubleshooting, and software installation.
10/2018 - 10/2019	Ameritas Position held: Customer Service Representative
	Assisted dental providers and members with policy information and claims.
11/2017 - 10/2018	Xtreme Cartage Position held: Freight Delivery Truck Driver
	 Managed a residential delivery route with a focus on timely deliveries within narrow windows.
05/2017 - 10/2017	United States Postal Service Position held: Training Supervisor
	 Trained new employees in compliance with safety policies. Supervised team in loading and unloading freight safely and timely.
01/2016 - 10/2016	Time Warner Cable Position held: Installation Technician
	 Worked independently in customer homes installing cable and internet. This required troubleshooting interference, working with various tech, soft skills with customers, strict time management, and a focus on a high success rate.
08/2014 - 01/2016	Self-Employed Position held: Consultant
	 Repaired and modified computer systems, software troubleshooting, custom computer system build-outs and systems integration consulting.

Other Relevant Experience

- United States Air Force Position: Aerospace Propulsion Jet Engine Journeyman
 - Supervised training programs and maintained aircraft technical orders.
 - Established work methods, production control, and performance standards.
 - Performed troubleshooting and inspections in accordance with repair and fault isolation manuals.
 - Investigated aircraft engine incidents that resulted in damage to equipment. Determined cause and calculated repair costs. Reported findings to lead commander.
 - Implemented Operational Risk Management (ORM) and LEAN improvements. Responsible for improving maintenance repair quality by 20%.
 - Monitored and maintained digital updates of more than 50 aircraft technical orders and job data guidelines.
 - Managed the Automated Data Processing Equipment, Government Purchase Card, and Hazardous Waste programs for my unit.
 - Managed the full contract lifecycle for multi-million dollar procurement of aircraft parts and support equipment as the assistant Supply Chain/Purchase Manager for a 265-person unit.
 - Provided on-the-job training, qualification, and proficiency training for engine maintenance personnel.

Education & Training

- LEAN (Six Sigma)
- Hazardous Materials Safety
- First-Aid & CPR

Additional Skills

- Proficient with Microsoft Windows OS, including troubleshooting and configuration.
- Proficient in Windows-based hardware, including troubleshooting, maintenance, and repair.
- Familiar with Altiris IT management software.